<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title><![CDATA[Asia Euro Synchronization (亚欧联合组织)]]></title>
  <subtitle><![CDATA[Education and Research Resources (教育研究资源)]]></subtitle>
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://szabouttimecoffe.com/"/>
  <updated>2015-03-04T02:57:54.582Z</updated>
  <id>http://szabouttimecoffe.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Nathan Zhu]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[blueshuchen@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://zespia.tw/hexo/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[联系我们 || Contact Us]]></title>
    <link href="http://szabouttimecoffe.com/2015/02/14/contact/"/>
    <id>http://szabouttimecoffe.com/2015/02/14/contact/</id>
    <published>2015-02-14T06:32:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2015-02-12T06:33:05.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="咨询时间_||_Hours_and_information">咨询时间 || Hours and information</h2>
<p>随时为你服务</p>
<p>We are available.  </p>
<p>在亚欧联合组织，我们乐意与你们交流。我们喜欢随时回答你们的问题。</p>
<p>At Asia Euro Synchronization, we like to communicate quickly. Send us a note or email and we will answer within 24 hours (sometimes even on weekends). And if it’s urgent, you can call us on our phone.</p>
<p>告诉我们你的经验</p>
<p>Tell us about your experience.</p>
<p>我们希望听到你对参加我们的活动有什么好的帮助和建议。</p>
<p>请发邮件：blueshuchen@gmail.com</p>
<p>We want to hear how your courses are progressing and how attending Asia Euro Synchronization has impacted your life. Is there something we can do better, or did we get something just right? Let us know.</p>
]]></content>
    <summary type="html">
    <![CDATA[<h2 id="咨询时间_||_Hours_and_information">咨询时间 || Hours and information</h2>
<p>随时为你服务</p>
<p>We are available.  </p>
<p>在亚欧联合组织，我们乐意与你们交流。我们喜欢]]>
    </summary>
    
      <category term="联系" scheme="http://szabouttimecoffe.com/tags/%E8%81%94%E7%B3%BB/"/>
    
      <category term="联系我们" scheme="http://szabouttimecoffe.com/categories/%E8%81%94%E7%B3%BB%E6%88%91%E4%BB%AC/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[关于我们 || About us]]></title>
    <link href="http://szabouttimecoffe.com/2015/02/13/About-us/"/>
    <id>http://szabouttimecoffe.com/2015/02/13/About-us/</id>
    <published>2015-02-13T02:08:24.000Z</published>
    <updated>2015-02-12T06:25:18.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="关于我们_||_About_us">关于我们 || About us</h2>
<h3 id="关于我们_||_About_us-1">关于我们 || About us</h3>
<p>亚欧联合组织是一个经验丰富的团队，我们致力于创建一个科技和商业相结合的专业团队。让亚洲和欧洲连接的更加紧密。</p>
<p>Asia-Euro Synchronization is an initiative created by a group of experienced technical and business professionals to connect Asia and Europe closer together.</p>
<p>在亚洲和欧洲的学术商业环境中，我们拥有深度而立体宽广的知识。我们的目标就是在学术和商业中建立一个技术的桥梁。<br>通过我们的努力，将高等院校，公司，各种组织间的交流联结起来。</p>
<p>With our diverse and wide set of knowledge about both the Asian and European academic and business environment, our aim is to form a technological transfer bridge between all participants. Through our activities, we strive to create a better technological future by enabling closer collaboration and knowledge exchange between universities, companies, supporting organizations and students from Asia and Europe. </p>
<p>我们相信，以下三个方面是我们共同发展的基石：合作教学，合作研究和集群合作。</p>
<p>We believe that three elements are required for a closer common development: Educational programs, research partnerships and cluster collaborations.<br>​<br>我们的合作教学项目是由我们的合作精英大学所主办的。学员可以到欧洲，近距离了解当地的工业环境，同时可以增强他们的专业技能。为今后的职业发展，和持续学习起到至关重要的作用和影响。</p>
<p>Our educational programs are executed in partnership with leading universities, allowing Asian students and professionals to travel to Europe. Participants gain a comprehensive insight into the local industrial situation while at the same time enhancing their professional skills and career prospects through additional education. </p>
<p>合作研究项目，工业产业和研究院可以深入合作。可以加速研究成果的转化。同时，让亚欧的公司可以结合各自的独有的能力创造更好的未来。</p>
<p>Research partnerships are enabled by connecting industrial and research institutes through common events. This broadens the scope and speed of technology transfer between all parties, allowing European and Asian companies to take advantage of each other’s unique abilities and features.</p>
<p>集群合作讲通过我们的合作网络来激励我们从国家之间合作到超越国际间合作的进化。</p>
<p>Cluster collaborations are encouraged on a national and supra-national level by leveraging our existing network of partners. </p>
<p>通过结合这个三个元素。我们相信我们有更好的未来，也将为世界做出自己的贡献</p>
<p>By combining all three elements, we believe that we can contribute to a stronger and better world.</p>
<hr>
<h3 id="我们的队伍和伙伴_||_Our_team_and_partners">我们的队伍和伙伴 || Our team and partners</h3>
<p><strong>Mr. Vangapandu V</strong> </p>
<p><img src="http://7u2o0y.com1.z0.glb.clouddn.com/Raj.jpeg" alt=""></p>
<p>CEO/Founder<br>AsiaEuroSync UG<br>SynergyRules Aerospace<br>Germany</p>
<p><strong>Dr. -Ing Daniel Hahn</strong></p>
<p><img src="http://7u2o0y.com1.z0.glb.clouddn.com/Daniel.jpeg" alt=""></p>
<p>CEO/Managing Director<br>APS GmbH<br>European Center for Mechatronics<br>​Germany</p>
<p><strong>Prof. Dr.-Ing. Günther Starke</strong></p>
<p><img src="http://7u2o0y.com1.z0.glb.clouddn.com/Gunther.jpeg" alt=""></p>
<p>FH Aachen University<br>APS GmbH<br>European Center for Mechatronics<br>​Germany</p>
<p><strong>Prof. Dr. Anoop Swaroop</strong></p>
<p><img src="http://7u2o0y.com1.z0.glb.clouddn.com/Anoop.png" alt=""></p>
<p>Professor<br>Monash University, Australia  </p>
<p>United Nations Representative , USA<br>Founder: Global Knowledge Alliance, Australia</p>
<p><strong>Mr. Philip Westphal</strong></p>
<p><img src="http://7u2o0y.com1.z0.glb.clouddn.com/Philip.jpeg" alt=""></p>
<p>CEO<br>WESTWERK GmbH &amp; Co. KG<br>Germany  </p>
<p><strong>朱述辰</strong></p>
<p><img src="http://7u2o0y.com1.z0.glb.clouddn.com/朱述辰.jpg" alt=""></p>
<p>CMEC Suzhou<br>中国区负责<br>联系: blueshuchen@gmail.com</p>
<hr>
<h3 id="通常的问题_||_Common_program_questions">通常的问题 || Common program questions</h3>
<p>我申请项目的时候是否会收到一封邀请函来帮助我获得签证？<br>Will participants receive an invitation letter to obtain their VISA?<br>是的。 我们会寄送邀请函帮助你成功申请签证。<br>Yes. A program invitation letter will be provided for successful applicants.</p>
<p>课程结构是怎样的？<br>How are lectures conducted?<br>课程是由我们拥有丰富经验的教授和业界具有丰富实践经验的工程师们对各位学员进行教学。教学地点是在我们的欧洲公司和合作工厂。<br>非常注重教育的互动和实践性。<br>Lectures are conducted at our European facilities by experienced professors and industry practitioners. Lectures are highly interactive and focused on maximum practical benefit.</p>
<p>哪些亚洲学校和结构可以派遣学生来参加我们的项目？<br>Which Asia universities or institutes are eligible to send students?</p>
<p>我们挑选参与的学校和机构是基于他们的简历和社会工作情况。如果你是一名学生或希望短期学习的工程师，请向你的教授或主管提出申请，我们可以代为沟通。<br>We select participants based on merit as shown in their CV. Partnering universities’ students will have an advantage if the merit based review seems inconclusive. If you are interested in having your university partner with us, let us know and we talk with your dean or professor.</p>
]]></content>
    <summary type="html">
    <![CDATA[<h2 id="关于我们_||_About_us">关于我们 || About us</h2>
<h3 id="关于我们_||_About_us-1">关于我们 || About us</h3>
<p>亚欧联合组织是一个经验丰富的团队，我们致力于创建一个科技和商业相结合的专业团队]]>
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Aboutout，关于，欧洲学习" scheme="http://szabouttimecoffe.com/tags/Aboutout%EF%BC%8C%E5%85%B3%E4%BA%8E%EF%BC%8C%E6%AC%A7%E6%B4%B2%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A0/"/>
    
      <category term="关于" scheme="http://szabouttimecoffe.com/categories/%E5%85%B3%E4%BA%8E/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[合作伙伴 || Partners]]></title>
    <link href="http://szabouttimecoffe.com/2015/02/12/partners/"/>
    <id>http://szabouttimecoffe.com/2015/02/12/partners/</id>
    <published>2015-02-12T04:09:30.000Z</published>
    <updated>2015-02-12T04:11:50.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="合作伙伴_||_Partners">合作伙伴 || Partners</h2>
<p><img src="http://7u2o0y.com1.z0.glb.clouddn.com/Syner.png" alt=""></p>
<p>SynergyRules 是一所杰出的综合性民营公司。专注于机械自动化的外包设计和解决方案。SynergyRules的核心支柱是解决速度，专业服务，良好客户沟通。在机械自动化的突破性技术领域中，已经有了很多成功的项目。现在，SynergyRules正在努力实习一流的控制系统和系统过程自动化技术。采用了卓越的IT技术和快速响应的电流技术需求。SynergyRules和其合作伙伴拥有丰富的经验。拥有各类专家为客户处理复杂的程序。</p>
<p>SynergyRules is an eminent integrated private company focused on process automation, outsourcing and outtasking solutions. SynergyRules believes in speed, professionalism and client communication as the core pillars of a successful business. The company has had ample experience in successfully managing Indo-European projects in the fields of process automation techniques and ground breaking technology solutions. SynergyRules strives to meet the current demands of companies trying to achieve process automation techniques with best in class control system systems, using a superior IT focus to enable system integrations per agile practices. SynergyRules and its partners have vast experience and are experts in handling numerous complex programs for their clients.</p>
<p><img src="http://7u2o0y.com1.z0.glb.clouddn.com/Scenter.jpeg" alt=""></p>
<p>SCTI 是Technology Transfer Network Centre of Steinbeis Foundation, 技术传播网络中心。用于德国和印度海德拉巴两间办公室。连接了850多个中心，不仅在欧洲，也是在其他国家，如中国，俄罗斯和新加坡的全球网络的一部分。终于专注于技术传播，并且拥有良好的资源（实验室和专家资源），因此，中心对于客户的业务可以提供专业的评估，对其全局进行进一步支持。中西还可以提供合同和项目管理方面的专业知识。</p>
<p>SCTI is a Technology Transfer Network Centre of Steinbeis Foundation, Germany, with its office at Hyderabad, India. It is a part of Global network connecting more than 850 Centres, not just in Europe, but also in other countries like China, Russia and Singapore. Each Centre specializes in its own stream of technology and has excellent resources in terms of laboratories and expert faculty. Hence the industry interested to outsource its technology development work with an institution does it at a fraction of cost involved – that if it were to borne the entire cost of its own. This is further backed by enormous knowledge resources, which can be assessed by each Centre by networking with its peer institutions within the Steinbeis network globally. The STCI provides its expertise in terms of contract and project management so as to provide the services in the most professional manner.</p>
<p><img src="http://7u2o0y.com1.z0.glb.clouddn.com/aps.jpeg" alt=""></p>
<p>APS GmbH，成立于1981年，总部设在亚琛，是欧洲的机电一体化中心。 APS有超过30年的机器人，传感器，信息和通信技术领域的开发经验。我们永远想要的经验丰富的技术工程师和跨学科的综合方法技术。微末的潜在客户，国家和国际工业合作伙伴，政府机构，研究院提供出色的解决方案。特别值得aps特别关注小型和中型的企业的创新技术引进和使用。通过在研发领域取得的丰富经验，APS在其中起着至关重要的作用。</p>
<p>APS GmbH, headquartered in Aachen was founded in 1981 and has been awarded as the European Centre for Mechatronics. APS has already more than 30 years of experience in the area of robotics, sensor technology, information and communication technology.  Developing these technologies with experienced engineers and technicians from various disciplines with multidisciplinary approaches, these solutions are provided to the potential clients in cooperation with national and international industrial partners, public authorities and researchers. A particular concern is to support small and medium-sized enterprises in the introduction and use of innovative technologies. By gaining vast experience in the field of research and development, APS plays a vital role in providing the top in seminars in recently advanced technologies.</p>
<p><img src="http://7u2o0y.com1.z0.glb.clouddn.com/compact.jpeg" alt=""></p>
<p>Compact Energy 是位于德国的太阳能公司。在全球范围拥有很多国际合作伙伴。设计太阳能业务及其他紧凑型能源。公司由德国企业家Mr. Alexander Krieg,位于德国北部西部地区，随着中小型太阳能产业的应用，公司必将在国际社会上起着更加重要的作用。</p>
<p>‘Compact Energy Energy mit Zukunft’ is the German based solar company which is playing a vital role in the solar business in global level along with its international partners.  The activities of Compact energies cover all the segments of solar business. Compact Energy was established a German entrepreneur Mr. Alexander Krieg, located at northern west region of Germany.   With the vast experience in the solar consulting, planning and integration of midlevel and large scale solar form’s, Compact Energies playing a vital role in the organizing this course along with the SynergyRules.</p>
<p><img src="http://7u2o0y.com1.z0.glb.clouddn.com/Commsure.jpeg" alt=""></p>
<p>CommSure致力于一站式培训解决方案。我们的培训方案涉及到所有教育机构，从个人，学校，培训中心，大中专院校，机构，大学和企业机构和跨国公司。随着我们精心制定ROTP™和TIME™方法，采用先进国家的技术辅助学习工具，我们为客户的每一步训练提供需要的解决方案。我们的离线和在线课程可以是客户的选择更为灵活，为各种机构和公司也可以提供灵活的培训服务。我们所拥有的独特的混合式学习模式是当今社会广泛接受的。</p>
<p>CommSure Knowledge Solutions is the one stop-shot for all training solutions. We cater to all educational institutions ranging from individuals, schools, coaching centres, colleges, institutions, Universities and corporate organizations and MNCs. With our well formulated ROTP™ and TIME™ methods, using state-of-the art technology-enabled learning tools, we provide a solution for every training need. Our offline and online programs come equipped to deliver need based training solutions across the spectrum of topics as needed by the individual, institution, or the organization. Our distinctive Blended Learning Model is today well accepted and used in the market. </p>
<p><img src="http://7u2o0y.com1.z0.glb.clouddn.com/Studentrank.png" alt=""></p>
<p><a href="http://www.thestudentranking.com/" target="_blank" rel="external">theStudentRanking.com</a>是全球领先的学生比较系统。提供10种语言，服务于50多个国家的学生，theStudentRanking.com为学生的技能和成就做一个诚实而准确的介绍，这种评价是相对于他或她的同侪团体，公司和组织的。我们也在世界范围内使用的各种系统来寻找，筛选和选择合格的候选人的教育活动和所处的位置，从而有可能为来自世界各地的考生去得到心目中的理想雇主或大学青睐。我们使用theStudentRanking.com选择参加我们的专属教育活动。请进入网站查询详情。</p>
<p>theStudentRanking.com是全球领先的学生比较系统。提供10种语言，并与来自50多个国家的学生，theStudentRanking.comprovides的个别人士的技能和成就一个诚实而准确的介绍相比，他或她的同侪团体。公司和组织在世界范围内使用的系统来寻找，筛选和选择合格的候选人的教育活动和内部位置，从而有可能为来自世界各地的考生通过心目中的理想雇主或大学被发现。我们使用<a href="http://www.thestudentranking.com/" target="_blank" rel="external">theStudentRanking.com</a>选择参加我们的专属教育活动。你可以在这里找到目前所有事件的概述。</p>
]]></content>
    <summary type="html">
    <![CDATA[<h2 id="合作伙伴_||_Partners">合作伙伴 || Partners</h2>
<p><img src="http://7u2o0y.com1.z0.glb.clouddn.com/Syner.png" alt=""></p>
<p>SynergyRules 是一]]>
    </summary>
    
      <category term="partners,aps" scheme="http://szabouttimecoffe.com/tags/partners-aps/"/>
    
      <category term="partners" scheme="http://szabouttimecoffe.com/categories/partners/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[项目 || programs]]></title>
    <link href="http://szabouttimecoffe.com/2015/02/12/program/"/>
    <id>http://szabouttimecoffe.com/2015/02/12/program/</id>
    <published>2015-02-11T23:57:10.000Z</published>
    <updated>2015-02-12T06:22:50.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>AutoSol 2015</p>
<p>这是一个短期的游学项目。 为亚洲的学生和工程师搭建一座桥梁。联通和欧洲中心的技术和学术工业领域。<br>​<br>This an initiative taken up by AsiaEuroSync, by understanding the actual importance of upgrading technological knowledge of Asia students/engineers and for a better technological future, we form a technology transfer bridge between Indian and European; academic and industry segments. </p>
<p>AutoSol，是一个难得机会，让学生和工程师能够有机会参与欧洲尖端的机械科学技术。ECE，EEE，CSE，”汽车机电一体化”。</p>
<p>AutoSol, will be the unique opportunity for students to obtain cutting edge European technology in the fields of  Mechanical, ECE, EEE, CSE, Automotive &amp; Mechatronics. AutoSol would be promising its participants unprecedented outlook into the technology world. </p>
<p>这一项目由四个方面组成：</p>
<p>This program mainly consisting 4 modules:</p>
<p>为期两天的研讨会：欧洲机电一体化研究室，在亚琛，AutoSol为未来的工程师提供了为了技术研讨会。参与研讨会的有德国知名的学者和专家。<br>同时，在会上，学生和工程师可以提交他们的论文。最好的三篇将会登载在我们的杂志上。</p>
<p>Two days of seminars at ‘European Labs for Mechatronics’, Aachen:  AutoSol also offers future oriented seminars for prospective engineers. Two day seminars are being offered by renowned German professors and industrial experts for an in-depth information of the present and future market conditions. These seminars would be taking place at the ‘European labs for Mechatronics’.<br>Student Conference: With this opportunity students can present their paper’s on various technological sectors related to Industrial Applications. Best three papers will be awarded and these papers will be published in our journal.</p>
<p>在汉诺威的交易研讨会，AutoSol提供了一个极好的机会，满足并与来自各个领域的业者。汽车制造商和他们的代表将在汉诺威工业展上交流体会，学生将参与国际就业市场。这种额外的好处是顶尖亚洲公司可以参与到国际交流中来。</p>
<p>Trade Fair &amp; Workshops at Hannover Messe 2015:  AutoSol offers an explicit opportunity to meet and interact with top companies from various fields, automotive manufacturers and their representatives in their respective outlets at Hannover Messe 2015. It followed with Career and Job fair, where student will expose to the International Job market. This additional advantage would be interacting top Asia companies as Asia as a partner country for this fair.</p>
<p>大众工厂之旅，参与德国最大的大众造车厂。</p>
<p>理解实际的造车技术。提供各种技术参考。</p>
<p>Volkswagen Manufacturing Plant Trip: There is also a one day Industrial trip to Volkswagen Manufacturing Pant in order to provide the participants with a brief idea of the biggest car manufacturing plant in Germany.<br>With these activities we are trying to provide the Research, Academic, Business- Career opportunities along with Industrial trip to manufacturing plant of Volkswagen</p>
<p>项目亮点：杰出的参与者将会有机会参加德国的4-6个实习项目。参与欧洲的机电一体化项目。</p>
<p>Program Highlights: Outstanding candidates go to Germany for our 4-6 Internship program at “European Center for Mechatronics, Aachen, Germany”</p>
<p>我们希望这一项目给你提供好的帮助，收到你们良好的反应。</p>
<p>We hope that, we will receive good response on this program from your students and organization. We will be glad to hear that.</p>
<p>具体事由请咨询：blueshuchen@gmail.com</p>
<p>For complete information and program brochure write us at blueshuchen@gmail.com​</p>
<p>注册申请请索取表格</p>
<p>To register for AutoSol 2015, fill up the form </p>
]]></content>
    <summary type="html">
    <![CDATA[<p>AutoSol 2015</p>
<p>这是一个短期的游学项目。 为亚洲的学生和工程师搭建一座桥梁。联通和欧洲中心的技术和学术工业领域。<br>​<br>This an initiative taken up by AsiaEuroSync, by understandin]]>
    </summary>
    
      <category term="项目" scheme="http://szabouttimecoffe.com/tags/%E9%A1%B9%E7%9B%AE/"/>
    
      <category term="项目" scheme="http://szabouttimecoffe.com/categories/%E9%A1%B9%E7%9B%AE/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[服务 || Services]]></title>
    <link href="http://szabouttimecoffe.com/2015/02/12/service/"/>
    <id>http://szabouttimecoffe.com/2015/02/12/service/</id>
    <published>2015-02-11T23:01:22.000Z</published>
    <updated>2015-02-12T06:02:51.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://7u2o0y.com1.z0.glb.clouddn.com/service.png" alt=""></p>
<h2 id="共建研究实验室_||_Research_Labs_Establishment">共建研究实验室 || Research Labs Establishment</h2>
<p>我们很荣幸的宣布，亚欧联合诅咒首先在印度和欧洲同步组织了一个研究实验室，支持着亚洲和欧洲之间的合作伙伴间的交流合作</p>
<p>It is our pleasure to announce that Asia-Euro Synchronization took a giant step to organize the establishment of research labs in India to support the Indian SME’s with the cooperation of European Research Partners.</p>
<p>我们现在的领域主要是工业自动化和机器人。我们也提供仿真软件和具备多种技术设备的实验室设施。同时，我们开始建立了远程自动化实验室。在亚洲的公司将会支持德国亚琛的欧洲机电一体化中心APS GmbH。</p>
<p>​We are initiating this in the field of Industrial Automation and Robotics. As a initial step of the current mission we are starting with establishment of Remote Automation labs at Indian university by providing the simulation software support and technology and research lab facilities support from German execution partner “European Centre for Mechatronics – APS GmbH”, located in Aachen, Germany. </p>
<h2 id="先进的工业机器人控制实验室_||_ARC_-_Advanced_Robotic_Control_Lab_for_Industrial_Applications">先进的工业机器人控制实验室 || ARC - Advanced Robotic Control Lab for Industrial Applications</h2>
<p>世界各地的大学都在不断提高更新自己的教育理念。为了学生们可以有充实的实践经验。让学生可以更加好的适应商务生活。</p>
<p>Universities worldwide improve their educational concepts continuously. However, they lack concrete training for job with hands-on experiences, so that the students are fit for the business life.</p>
<p>亚欧同步组织组织建立研发实验室，率先在印度和德国亚琛的欧洲机电一体化中心的APS GmbH展开。还有德国的‘Steinbeis Center for Technology Transfer’提供技术支持。这样做的目的是教机器人在亚洲的大学，与工业产业中的机器人公司可以有更广泛的合作。让教育理念更新。让亚洲的工业，包括中小企业提供的真实的生产要求进行测试的自动化解决方案。另外，也间接参与全球研究计划的未来。</p>
<p>Asia Euro Synchronization tackles this problem and organizes the establishment of R&amp;D labs in India, with the worldwide renowned partners ‘APS GmbH – European Centre for Mechatronics’, Germany and ‘Steinbeis Center for Technology Transfer’, India. The aim is to enhance the current education by introducing concrete industrial automation concepts by teaching robotics at Asia universities, with access to real industrial robot. Further, these labs can support Asia industries including SMEs by providing automation solutions tested under real production requirements. In addition, the gap is bridged to participate at global research programs in the future.</p>
<p>详细的申请条件详细咨询:blueshuchen@gmail.com</p>
<p>下发是率先开展的印度大学条件，其他地方请发邮件详细咨询。</p>
<p>An initial step for the implementation, ARC had already been organizing regular student seminars in Germany including workshops and live experiments at APS in Germany. ARC provides the students the access to industrial robotics under production conditions with remote control. An extensive exchange program for Indian faculty members guarantees the high quality of the educational lessons and practical courses. These practical courses allow direct control of the industrial robots in Germany from Indian universities. Concretely, the students learn simulating, programming and controlling in order to test their results at these industrial robots, which are equipped with grippers, sensors etc.</p>
<p>Applied Robotics Control for Industrial Automation:<br>Each participating university receives a software access for simulation and control of industrial robots.<br>Students learn individually and as a team to solve concrete industrial tasks which are splits into various suitable sub-tasks for immediate learning success. These tasks are supervised by trained Indian faculty members along with remotely participating German experts.<br>The automation tasks are designed and developed in cooperation with the Indian faculty members.<br>​<br>Requirement for Indian University:<br>Indian University/College need be a member of Indo-Euro Synchronization academic cluster. For further inquiries on obtaining the membership please contact us at consult@indoeurosync.com</p>
<p>Benefits of the Membership and Remote robotic lab at Indian University:<br> Member of our Academic cluster will receive the necessary training for their faculty members at Germany to run this program<br> Software and its server support will be provided to members of the universities to establish automation lab facilities at their location<br> These universities are the premium members of our near future Automation Cluster in India to execute the industrial and research projects in next days.<br> Trained students will be the first point of contact for internship positions and jobs in our projects and partner automation industries from India and Germany.</p>
]]></content>
    <summary type="html">
    <![CDATA[<p><img src="http://7u2o0y.com1.z0.glb.clouddn.com/service.png" alt=""></p>
<h2 id="共建研究实验室_||_Research_Labs_Establishment">共建研究实验室 || Resea]]>
    </summary>
    
      <category term="服务，研究室，机器人" scheme="http://szabouttimecoffe.com/tags/%E6%9C%8D%E5%8A%A1%EF%BC%8C%E7%A0%94%E7%A9%B6%E5%AE%A4%EF%BC%8C%E6%9C%BA%E5%99%A8%E4%BA%BA/"/>
    
      <category term="服务" scheme="http://szabouttimecoffe.com/categories/%E6%9C%8D%E5%8A%A1/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
